Once again, congratulations.
Thank you. I'm super excited. We're
excited to have you.
We're going to kick things off with Mike
Kaye, followed by Joe Person.
Hey Sam, congrats. I know it's been
probably a long day.
Um
what has the day really been like for
you and your family and how much
did you talk to the Panthers before they
picked you today?
Yeah, I mean today's been just filled
with family really. I just all was
settled down watching the draft, I just
waiting for my name to be called. Um
I had a Zoom with the Panthers. Um so we
we we were in touch.
Um but yeah, super excited.
You obviously have a lot of athleticism.
You're not necessarily the most
prototypical center size, but I know you
a lot of analysts rave about your
technique and you were two-year starter.
How much did those first few years of
the program kind of
kind of establish the way you wanted to
attack the game and is there a guy you
kind of modeled your game after?
Yeah, I mean I came in at Kansas State
as a walk-on. So I kind of came with the
mentality just to give it my all, try my
best and improve daily. Um so
and I looked up to the guy named Cooper
Beebe. He's with the Cowboys right now.
He was an older guy at K-State. He he
did everything the right way. Um he's a
great mentor. Um but yeah, I think that
kind of contributed to my
my game and I'm just excited to learn
more
um as I get to the next level
level and just compete.
Thanks. Congrats again.
Thank you.
>> Sam, how you doing, man? It's Joe Person
with The Athletic. Congrats.
Can you hear me?
>> Hey, how's it going?
Thank you.
Hey, um How you yep.
So, were you surprised you had to wait
as long as you did? Like I know our
draft analyst had you rated second
center right behind Slaughter who who
went in the second round. Were were you
surprised you had to wait to the fifth?
Um yeah, I was a little surprised.
Um
I was kind of hearing I would be like um
third round early day three. Um but you
know,
everything happens for a reason. God has
a plan. So I'm just excited
thrilled to get to work.
How did you kind of like keep yourself
from, you know, like going up the wall
and and getting a little stir crazy over
the weekend?
Uh
I mean, I had my fiancee by my side. So
we were just sitting there together.
We were comforting each other.
Nice. Hey, um you talked about your your
walk-on journey. I also read that you
gained like 50 lb over five seasons uh
in Manhattan. Was was that accurate and
and how did you do it if so?
Uh it's kind of accurate, yeah. Um
So like my
last game
high school
I was like 240 to 85. So I gained quite
a bit of weight between
between the time of my last game and I
got to K-State and that was just
pounding PB&Js at night. Just eating
whatever I can. I knew I needed to gain
weight. So I put my mind to it.
You said 45 lb, right?
Around yeah, about 45 lb, yeah. Okay.
Thank you, man. Obviously wasn't the
best way. Yep. Yep.
Cast.
Hey Sam, congratulations.
Can you hear me? Thank you. Thank you.
Um I hear you.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but you didn't
allow a single sack in college. Is that
correct?
I think that's correct, yes. But that's
that's just the guys that are around me.
I had some good great guys around me.
The quarterback, you know, he was able
to save me a few times, but
I mean, but kind of on that note, how
much of a point of pride is that? I
mean, as an offensive lineman, that
being kind of your main job and and at
what point did you realize there was a
chance to finish college with that stat
next your name?
Yeah, I mean,
100%. I mean, as an offensive lineman,
you kind of got that protector
mentality. So that's our job to protect
and defend our quarterback and fight for
them. Um
And I I really didn't try to
stay in touch with that. I didn't really
look at that. I just went in with each
day, each game just trying to do my
best.
Awesome. Thank you.
Any more questions for Sam?
Thank you.
When is the wedding?
All right, Sam.
>> that, sorry? Oh, it's Sam. When when is
the wedding?
Oh, it's coming up.
All right, Sam. Um June 20th.
Oh, nice.
Congratulations.
What Where is it?
Thank you. Thank you.
It's in Florida.
Florida on the beach. It's
just a family wedding, small, intimate.
Yep.
Nice.
All right, Sam. Thank you so much for
taking the time to talk to us and once
again, congratulations.
Thank you. Thank you. It was a pleasure.
>> Sam, no problem. We can't wait to have
you here in Carolina.
>> [music]
[music]